Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6: Reviews and Publicity, 6
  - Subseries 6.04: Press, 6.04
    - New Technologie in the Arts. ART Scan. Vol 20. No. 1 Jan-Feb 2001 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - SF Weekly: Reel World Article August 8-14, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - The Social Life of Digital Art. Berkeley Art Museum article. September 23, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Technology meets Art. UC Davis Magazine. p.26 Fall 2001 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Studio Notes: the journal of working artists. No. 34 October-December 2001 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Masquerades. 14th Virginia Film Festival. October 25-28,2001 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - SF Weekly: Reel World Article January 3-9. 2001 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - "Hollywood North?" Engineering Progress UC Davis. P.6 Spring 2001 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Koch Gallery Newsletter Winter 2001/2002 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Rencontres Internationales de Cinema a Paris October 31, 2001-November 11, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - "Sundance: Less Buzz, More Deals" Rick Luman. New York Times. January 21, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - "Full 'Dance Card'" Toddy McCarthy. Daily Variety November 27, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - "Sundance Names Film Lineup" SAP2IT.com/SF Chronicle November 28, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - "Sundance Names Entries for.." Kirk Honeycutt. Hollywood Reporter. November 27, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - 7x7 SF Magazine. Premiere Issue September 2001 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - "Op Art: Collaboration | This is not a Pipe" UCLArts. Vol. 4, No. 2. p.8-9 Spring 2001 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - 1994 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - 1995 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - 1996 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - 1998 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - 25th Festival International du Film de Flandre October 6-17, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - 1999 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Leonardo (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - SF & the Grande Dame of Digital Art June 1999 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Parabola 1999 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - "Can You Digit?" November 1999 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - "Jag satter guldkant pa..." 1999 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - "Visual Artist Lynn Hershman Leeson" February 1999 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - "Jewels of the Bay" November 1999 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - "Makers of Three Successful New..." October 1999 (Box 107, Folder 8)